University of Connecticut, Thomas J. Dodd Research Center Records 1998.0290
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series III: Program Records, undated, 1992-
  - Book fair, 2000
    - Sketch (McCurdy) (Box 8)
    - Terri's File (Box 6:363)
  - Book fair, 2001
    - Agendas and Minutes (Box 6:364)
    - Flyer (Box 21:, Folder 633)
    - Flyer Mailing (Box 6:365)
    - Friday lecture/Reception (Box 6:366)
    - Program (Box 21:, Folder 632)
    - Terri's file (incl. Raab Prize) (Box 6:367)
  - Book fair, 2002
    - Brochure (Box 21:, Folder 634)
    - Flyer (Box 21:, Folder 635)
    - Jean's file (Box 6:368)
    - Program (Box 21:, Folder 636)
    - Terri's file (incl. Raab Prize) (Box 6:369)
  - Book fair, 2003
    - Agendas (Box 6:370)
    - Favor (Dinner) (Box 6:371)
    - Flyer (Spanish) (Box 21:, Folder 637)
    - Program (Box 6:372)
    - Program (Box 21:, Folder 638)
    - Publicity (Box 6:373)
    - Raab Prize (Box 6:374)
  - Book fair, 2004
    - Program (Box 21:, Folder 672)
    - Volunteers (Box 21:, Folder 672a)
  - Book fair, 2005
    - Promoting Literacy Workshop (includes program, report, correspondence) (Box 22:, Folder 692)
    - Publicity (Box 19:, Folder 616)
    - Terri's File (Box 19:, Folder 616a)
  - Book fair, 2006
    - Bookbag (Box 21:, Folder 678)
    - Dinner (Box 21:, Folder 679)
    - Postcard (Box 21:, Folder 675)
    - Teacher's Conference Terri's file (Box 22:, Folder 709)
    - Terri's file (Box Box 22:, Folder 706)
    - Raab prize (Box Box 22:, Folder 706a)
  - Book fair, 2007
    - Teacher's Conference TD Banknorth request (Box 22:, Folder 710)
    - Terri's file (Box 22:, Folder 707)
    - Raab prize (Box 22:, Folder 707a)
    - Program and Invitation (Box 22:, Folder 707b)
  - Book fair, 2008
    - Terri's file (Box 22:, Folder 708)
    - Raab prize (Box 22:, Folder 708a)
    - Program, Invitation and postcard (Box 22:, Folder 708b)
  - Heroism, Nationalism and Human Rights Conference, 2005-2006 (Box 16:, Folder 619)
  - Honorary Degrees
    - DePaola, Tomie, 1999 (Box 6:375)
  - Kathleen Krull and Jane Dyer, 2004 (Box 21:, Folder 668)
  - Lecture Series
    - RBS Greenwich Capitol Economic Seminar
      - Greenspan, Alan, 1997 (Box 6:376)
      - Summers, Lawrence, 1999 (Box 6:377)
      - Raines, Franklin, 2000 (Box 16:, Folder 590)
      - Raines, Franklin, 2000 (Box 21:, Folder 639)
      - Rowland, John G., 2002 (Box 16:581)
      - Senator Phil Gramm, Ambassador Felix Rohatyn, 2004 (Box 16:, Folder 582)
      - Senator Phil Gramm, Ambassador Felix Rohatyn, 2004 (Box 21:, Folder 667)
      - Fisher, Peter, 2003 March (Box 6:378)
      - Fisher, Peter, 2003 (Box 16:, Folder 591)
      - Donaldson, William H., 2003 November (Box 6:379)
      - deSoto, Hernando, 2005 September 26 (Box 19:, Folder 608)
    - Raymond and Beverly Sackler Series
      - Mitchell, George, 1998 (Box 6:380)
      - Lee, Henry C., 2000 (Box 16:574)
      - Lee, Henry C., 2000 (Box 21:641)
      - Robert F. Drinan, S.J., 2001 (Box 16:575)
      - Robert F. Drinan, S.J., 2001 (Box 21:642)
      - Lederberg, Joshua, 2002 (Box 16:583)
      - Lederberg, Joshua, 2002 (Box 21:643)
      - Power, Samantha, 2003 (Box 16:, Folder 584)
      - Power, Samantha, 2003 (Box 21:, Folder 644)
      - Marrus, Michael R., 2004 (Box 16:579)
      - Ignatieff, Michael, 2004 (Box 16:, Folder 585)
      - Ignatieff, Michael, 2004 (Box 21:, Folder 622)
      - Bang-Jensen, Nina, 2005 April (Box 16:, Folder 592)
      - Marrus, Michael, 2005 October 6 (Box 19:, Folder 610)
      - Ferencz, Benjamin, 2005 November 7 (Box 19:, Folder 615)
    - Edwin Way Teale
      - Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 6:382)
      - Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 6:383)
      - Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 6:384)
      - Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 6:385)
      - Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 6:386)
      - Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 6:387)
      - Programs, 2001-2002 (Box 7:388)
      - Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 27)
      - Programs, 2002-2003 (Box 7:389)
      - Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 27)
      - Planning, 2003-2004 (Box 7:390)
      - Programs, 2003-2004 (Box 14:580)
      - Programs, 2004 (Box 16:, Folder 580)
      - Planning, 2004-2005 (Box 27)
      - Programs, 2004 (Box 21:, Folder 669)
      - Planning, 2005-2006 (Box 27)
      - Programs, 2005 (Box 22:, Folder 694)
      - Planning, 2006-2007 (Box 27)
      - Posters, 1999-2004 (Box 8:416)
  - Pins--Logo, circa 2004 (Box 21:, Folder 663)
  - Programs
    - Cseh, Gene, undated (Box 7:391)
    - Dodd Prize, 2003
      - Agendas (Box 7:392)
      - Biographies (Box 7:393)
      - Budget (Box 7:394)
      - Citation (Box 7:395)
      - Correspondence (Box 7:396)
      - Exhibit, 2003 (Box 8:417)
      - Guest List (Box 7:397)
      - Program (Box 7:398)
      - Program (Box 21:666)
      - Publicity (Box 7:399)
      - Publicity, 2003 (Box 8:418)
      - Security (Box 7:400)
      - Speeches (Box 7:401)
    - Dodd Prize, 2005
      - Dodd Prize in International Justice and Human Rights, 2005 October 17 (Box 19:, Folder 611)
    - James Marshall Day, 2002 (Box 7:402)
    - JPEG2000 in Libraries and Archives Conference, 2004 (Box 7:, Folder 590)
    - JPEG2000 in Libraries and Archives Conference, 2004 (Box 21:, Folder 621)
    - Ladd, Everett Carll, Jr., 1999 (Box 7:403)
    - Witthus, Rutherford W. Retirement, 2004 (Box 21:, Folder 671)
  - Sixtieth Anniversary of the Judgment at Nuremberg: Whitney Harris, 2006 April 10 (Box 16:, Folder 618)
  - Sixtieth Anniversary of the Judgment at Nuremberg: Whitney Harris, 2006 April 10 (Box 21:, Folder 676)
  - Tenth Anniversary Celebration, 2005 August - December
    - Claribel Alegria Lecture, 2005 September 27 (Box 19:, Folder 609)
    - Annual Report (1995-2005) (Box 19:, Folder 599)
    - Book Fair Publicity, 2005 (Box 19:, Folder 616)
    - Calendar of Events, 2005 (Box 19:, Folder 598)
    - Connecticut State Historical Records Advisory Board Resolution, 2005 (Box 19:, Folder 597)
    - Dodd Prize in International Justice and Human Rights, 2005 October 17 (Box 19:, Folder 611)
    - Dodd Research Center Exhibit, 2005 (Box 19:, Folder 605)
    - Economic Rights Conference, 2005 October 27 - 29 (Box 19:, Folder 612)
    - Economic Rights Conference Publicity, 2005 October 27 - 29 (Box 19:, Folder 613)
    - Bob Englehart lecture, 2005 September 22 (Box 19:, Folder 607)
    - General Publicity, 2005 (Box 19:, Folder 596)
    - Greenwich Capital Lecture, Hernando deSoto, 2005 September 26 (Box 19:, Folder 608)
    - Human Rights Initiative Calendar of Events (Fall 2005) (Box 19:, Folder 600)
    - Logo Proposals, 2005 (Box 19:, Folder 594)
    - NCLC Endowment Thank You, 2005 (Box 19:, Folder 595)
    - "A Night with the Blues and Lots More" program, 2005 November 1 (Box 19:, Folder 614)
    - Sackler Lecture, Benjamin Ferencz, 2005 November 7 (Box 19:, Folder 615)
    - Sackler Lecture, Michael Marrus, 2005 October 6 (Box 19:, Folder 610)
    - Semester Scrap Book by Mary Wilsted, 2005 (Box 19:, Folder 617)
    - Tomie dePaola Honorary Degree Ceremony--Weekend programs, 1999 October (Box 27)
    - UConn Libraries Newsletter, 2005 February/March (Box 19:, Folder 601)
    - UConn Libraries Newsletter & Anniversary Insert, 2005 April/May (Box 19:, Folder 602)
    - UConn Libraries Newsletter, 2005 September/October (Box 19:, Folder 603)
    - UConn Libraries Newsletter, 2005 November/December (Box 19:, Folder 604)
    - UConn Traditions, "UConn's Hidden Treasures,", 2004 (Box 21:, Folder 680)
    - UConn-ANC Comparative Human Rights Conference, 2000 (Box 21:, Folder 645)
    - "What's Past is Prologue" program, 2005 September 21 (Box 19:, Folder 606)
  - Book Fair, 2009
    - Terri's file, 2009 (Box 35)
    - Raab Prize for writing, 2009-2010 (Box 35)
  - Book Fair, 2010 (Box 35)
    - Terri's file, 2010 (Box 35)
    - Raab Prize, 2010 (Box 35)
  - Book Fair, 2011
    - Terri's file, 2011 (Box 35)
    - Fundraising, 2011 (Box 35)
    - Raab Prize, 2011 (Box 35)
- Series IV: Publications, undated, 1976-
  - Alternative Press Collection, undated (Box 7:404)
  - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 16:, Folder 587)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 16:, Folder 588)
  - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 16:, Folder 589)
  - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 7:409)
  - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 21:, Folder 623)
  - Annual Report, 2003 (Box 7:410)
  - Fielding Dawson Broadside, 2002 (Box 21:, Folder 665)
  - Filing and Recordkeeping, 1985 (Box 7:405)
  - Literary Collections, 1976 (Box 7:406)
  - Editing the Maximus Poems, 1983 (Box 7:407)
  - Holiday Cards (Box 7:408)
    - 199? (Box 22:, Folder 690)
    - circa 2000 (Box 21:, Folder 627)
    - 2001 (Box 21:, Folder 628)
    - 2005 (Box 22:, Folder 691)
    - 2006 (Box 21:, Folder 664)
  - Northeast Children's Literature Collection, circa 1985 (Box 22:, Folder 703)
  - Opportunities for Support, circa 2000 (Box 21:, Folder 625)
  - Thomas J. Dodd Research Center at the University of Connecticut dedicated to preserving the past while preparing for the future, circa 1994 (Box 22:, Folder 705)
  - Tikvah, 1999 (Box OS)
  - Book Fair Poster, 2008 (Box OS)
- Series V: Predecessor Departments, undated, 1965-1997
  - Special Collections
    - 25th Anniversary materials, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 693)
    - Annual Reports, 1965-1981 (Box 7:420)
    - Annual Reports, 1981-1987 (Box 7:421)
    - Annual Reports, 1987-1995 (Box 22:, Folder 689)
    - Collection Development Policy, 1977-1978 (Box 7:422)
    - Funds/Donors, 1992-1993 (Box 7:423)
    - Funds, 1985-1987 (Box 7:424)
    - Funds, 1980-1983 (Box 7:425)
    - Gift Records, 1968-1986 (Box 7:426)
    - Gifts
      - 1965-1975 (Box 7:427)
      - 1976-1981 (Box 7:428)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 7:429)
      - 1981-1985 (Box 7:430)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 7:431)
      - 1987-1989 (Box 7:432)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 7:433)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 7:434)
      - 1993-1996 (Box 9:435)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 9:436)
    - Gift Procedures, 1989-1996 (Box 9:437)
    - Personnel Allocation Review, 1992 (Box 21:, Folder 620)
    - Publishers' Bindings and Designs, 1970 (Box 9:438)
    - Statistics, 1975-1982 (Box 9:439)
    - Statistics, 1982-1987 (Box 9:440)
  - Historical Manuscripts and Archives
    - Archives Planning
      - Arts Commission committee, 1991-1993 (Box 9:441)
      - Buildings and facilities, 1980-1988 (Box 9:442)
      - Collecting Policies Task Forces, 1989 (Box 9:443)
      - Committe files, 1987-1989 (Box 9:444)
      - Committe files, 1988-1989 (Box 9:445)
      - Committe files, 1911-1992 (Box 9:446)
      - Committee final report, 1991 (Box 9:447)
      - Compact shelving, 1989-1992 (Box 9:448-449)
      - Department of Public Works, 1992 (Box 9:451)
      - Design, 1991-1992 (Box 9:452)
      - Designs - Other buildings, 1989-1990 (Box 9:453)
      - Development Office, 1989-1991 (Box 9:454)
      - Dodd, Christopher, 1991-1992 (Box 9:455)
      - Environmental Controls, 1992 (Box 9:456)
      - Environmental issues and designs, 1985 (Box 9:457)
      - Exhibit Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 9:458)
      - Facilities office, 1991-1992 (Box 9:459)
      - Faculty responses, 1989 (Box 9:460)
      - Fletcher, Thompson, 1991 (Box 9:461)
      - Fletcher, Thompson, 1991-1992 (Box 9:462)
      - Fletcher, Thompson, 1992 (Box 9:463)
      - Fundraising and development, undated, 1992 (Box 9:464)
      - Jimmerson, Rand, 1987-1990 (Box 9:465)
      - Jimmerson, Rand, 1991-1992 (Box 9:466)
      - Lull, 1992 (Box 9:467)
      - Massachusetts, 1988 (Box 9:468)
      - Meeting minutes and notes, 1989 (Box 9:469)
      - Memoranda/Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11:470)
      - Michigan, 1988 (Box 11:471)
      - Minnesota, 1988 (Box 11:472)
      - Mission Task Force, 1989 (Box 11:473)
      - Project Description, 1989 (Box 11:474)
      - Report, 1989 (Box 11:475)
      - Report, 1991 (Box 11:476)
    - Archives Research Center, 1987-1989 (Box 11:477)
    - Archives Research Center Advisory Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 11:478)
    - Audio-visual, 1992 (Box 11:533)
    - Brochure, 1991-1993 (Box 11:534)
    - Collection move, mapping sheets, 1995-1996 (Box 21:, Folder 647-662)
    - Connecticut Historical and Publications Commission Index, 199?-2003 (Volume V. 12)
    - Connecticut Labor
      - AFL-CIO - Memorabilia, undated (Box 11:479)
      - AFL-CIO - Organization, 1982 (Box 11:480)
      - AFSCME Local 749, 1984 (Box 11:481)
      - AFSCME Local 1303-115, 1984 (Box 11:482)
      - AFSCME Local 1565, 1984 (Box 11:483)
      - AFSCME Local 1942, 1984 (Box 11:484)
      - AFSCME Local 3394, 1984 (Box 11:485)
      - AFT 3837, 1984 (Box 11:486)
      - Brass Workers History Project, 1980-1982 (Box 11:487)
      - Bridgeport Public Library - Labor Records project, 1976 (Box 11:488)
      - Building Trades, Connecticut State Council, 1983 (Box 11:489)
      - Carpenters Local 43, 1984 (Box 11:490)
      - Central Connecticut Typographical #679, 1984 (Box 11:492)
      - Clothing and Textile Workers Local 125, 1983-1984 (Box 11:493)
      - Connecticut Labor History Society, 1983 (Box 11:491)
      - Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, 1984 (Box 11:494)
      - Connecticut Workers and Technological Change, 1980-1982 (Box 11:495)
      - Electrical Workers Local 1040, 1984 (Box 11:496)
      - Fire Fighters Local 1339, 1984 (Box 11:497)
      - Food and Commercial Workers Union Local 371, 1983 (Box 11:498)
      - Hartford-New Britain Building Trades Council, 1984 (Box 11:499)
      - Health Care Employees District 1199, 1980-1984 (Box 11:500)
      - International Typographers Union Local 47, 1984 (Box 11:501)
      - International Typographical Union, 1983-1984 (Box 11:502)
      - Loabor - Hoffman, Alice, 1980-1981 (Box 11:503)
      - Labor Archives - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 11:504)
      - Labor Archives - Projects, 1984-1985 (Box 11:505)
      - Labor Education Center, 1987 (Box 11:506)
      - Labor Education Local 189, 1983-1984 (Box 11:507)
      - Laborers' Local 665, 1984 (Box 11:508)
      - Letter Carriers, 1984 (Box 11:509)
      - Machinists Lodge 1249, 1984 (Box 11:510)
      - Musicians Local 186, 1984 (Box 11:511)
      - New Britain Central Labor Council, 1984 (Box 11:512)
      - Ohio Labor History project, 1980 (Box 11:513)
      - Pogue, Don, 1984 (Box 11:514)
      - Postal Workers, 1985 (Box 11:515)
      - Rubber Workers Local 45, 1983-1984 (Box 11:516)
      - United Rubber Workers #93, 1984 (Box 11:517)
      - Sheetmetal Workers Local 563, 1984 (Box 11:518)
      - Waterbury Central Labor Council, 1984 (Box 11:519)
      - Wayne State University Archives of Labor and Urban Affairs, 1983 (Box 11:520)
    - Hartford Courant Index, 1984 (Box 11:521)
    - Labor Project Final report, 1991 (Box 11:522)
    - Labor Project publicity, 1983 (Box 11:523)
    - Photographic Services, 1990-1993 (Box 13:557)
    - Physical Plant, 1990-1992 (Box 11:524)
    - Planning Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 11:525)
    - Planning Committee minutes, 1991 (Box 11:526)
    - Planning Committee (Library), 1991 (Box 11:527)
    - Polish-Jewish Archives, 1987-1989 (Box 11:528-529)
    - Project Planning Guide, 1989 (Box 11:530)
    - Project Planning Guide, 1992 (Box 11:531)
    - Public Opinion Survey Records, 1988 (Box 11:532)
    - Records Management
      - 1994-1995 (Box 11:533)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 11:534)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 11:535)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 11:536)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 11:537)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 11:538)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 11:539)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 11:540)
    - Reference--Railroad, 1986-1993 (Box 11:541)
    - Reference--Voter Registration Records, 1977-1993 (Box 13:561)
    - Reference
      - 1981-1991 (Box 11:542)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 11:543)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 13:544)
      - 1986 (Box 13:545)
      - 1987 (Box 13:546)
      - 1988 (Box 13:547)
      - 1989 (Box 13:548)
      - 1990 (Box 13:549)
      - 1991 (Box 13:550)
      - 1992 (Box 13:551)
      - 1993 (Box 13:552)
      - 1994 (Box 13:553)
      - 1994 August (Box 13:554)
      - 1995 January - June (Box 13:555)
      - 1995 July - December (Box 13:556)
    - Reference Use Statistics
      - 1980-1988 (Box 22:, Folder 688)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 22:, Folder 687)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 22:, Folder 686)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 22:, Folder 685)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 22:, Folder 684)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 22:, Folder 683)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 22:, Folder 682)
    - Security, 1992-1993 (Box 13:558)
    - Special Collections, 1992 (Box 13:559)
    - Stacks, 1991-1992 (Box 13:560)
    - University of Connecticut Index, undated (Box 10)
- Series VI: Media, undated, -
  - Media (photos, slides, negatives), undated (Box 17)
  - History of the Library slides, undated (Box 8)
  - DRC Talk Slides, undated (Box 8)
  - Media - 2005-2007 Addition (photos, digital files, videos), undated (Box 18)
    - Kennelly/Silverman Lecture (CD of images), 2007 February 8
    - American Montessori Society Archives Reception (CD of images), 2006 October 28
    - Teale Lecture Series, David Sibley (CD of images), 2007 April 18
    - Nancy Johnson donation (CD of images), 2007 Spring/Summer
    - Dodd Prize/ Letters from Nuremberg Readings (CDs, photographs, albums), 2007, October 1
    - Connecticut Children's Book fair (CD of images), 2007 November 10-11
    - Cd of Dodd Prize, windows media player file (2 cds), October 5, 2009
    - Dodd Center Talk - includes slides and transcript, 1996
  - Political Collections brochure CD, 2006 (Box 21:, Folder 677)
  - Video cassettes
    - Konover dedication. Ness, Joseph. Schwartz, Jerry. Kobulnicky, Paul. Kessler, Stanley. Hartley, Harry J.; Poupko, Yehiel E.; Greenberg, Irving. Konover, Simon. Rosen, James. Rosenthal, Jodi. Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, [1996] (Other Video 186)
    - Connecticut History Online. WVIT-TV (Television station: Hartford, Conn.), [2002] (Other Video 197)
    - Breaking ground for history: ceremonies to mark the groundbreaking for the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut, Storrs, Connecticut, 1993 October 10 (Other Video 221)
    - A look back at a year of introspection / producer, Mark J. Roy. Dodd year retrospective. A montage of Dodd Center events concerning human rights from the 1995-1996 school year. Includes footage of Bill Clinton's speech at the dedication of the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, Simon Konover and others speaking at panel of Holocaust survivors, a panel on Executive Order 9066, the order that caused the internment of Japanese-Americans during the Second World War, a speech by Cornell West on race, Dith Pran talking on the Cambodia n killing fields, and Madeline Albright on Rwanda (Other Video 226)
    - Dodd Prize 2003. Thomas J. Dodd Prize. Speakers, Ambassador Thomas J. Dodd, Jr., Senator Christopher Dodd, Prime Minister Bertie Ahern, Deputy Prime Minister John Prescott (accepting for Prime Minister Blair). Ceremony for the awarding of the first Thomas J. Dodd Prize in International Justice and Human Rights to Prime Minister Bertie Ahern and Prime Minister Tony Blair for their work on the Good Friday Peace Accords (Other Video 248)
    - Thomas Dodd and Legacy of Nuremburg, 2008 (Other Video 396)
    - Greenwich Capital Lecture Allen Weinstein and "Reflections on Archives and Democracy", 2008 (Other Video 395)
    - Greenwich Capital Lecture Allen Weinstein and "Reflections on Archives and Democracy", 2008 (Other DVD 98)
    - Sackler Lecture, Judge Patricia Wald, 2008 (Other Video 393)
    - Mini DV tapes of Dodd Prize (2 tapes), 2007 or 2009 (Box 18)
    - Mini DV tape of Dodd Prize, October 1, 2007 (Box 18)